<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/ClubGearHubWebsite/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/ClubGearHubWebsite/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-12-07T22:00:08+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/ClubGearHubWebsite/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ClubGearHub</title><subtitle>ClubGearHub optimizes equipment management for clubs, ensuring efficient use and resources for club activities by systematically managing and tracking equipment.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Announcing ClubGearHub Open Source Website</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/ClubGearHubWebsite/2023/12/07/announcing-clubgearhub-open-source-website.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Announcing ClubGearHub Open Source Website" /><published>2023-12-07T01:21:20+09:00</published><updated>2023-12-07T01:21:20+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/ClubGearHubWebsite/2023/12/07/announcing-clubgearhub-open-source-website</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/ClubGearHubWebsite/2023/12/07/announcing-clubgearhub-open-source-website.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello ClubGearHub community,</p>

<p>We’re excited to announce the launch of the official ClubGearHub Open Source Website! This platform has been created to enhance the overall experience for our community members and contributors. Here’s a brief overview of the key pages you’ll find on our website:</p>

<ol>
  <li>
    <p>About<br />
Learn more about the vision, mission, and goals of ClubGearHub. Discover the story behind the project and get to know the passionate individuals driving its development.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>Features<br />
Explore the rich set of features that make ClubGearHub a powerful tool for clubs and organizations. From convenient equipment management to real-time tracking, we’ve designed ClubGearHub with efficiency and optimization in mind.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>Contact<br />
Have questions or feedback? The Contact page is your direct line to the ClubGearHub team. Reach out to us with your inquiries, suggestions, or just to say hello. We value your input and look forward to hearing from you.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>Community<br />
Connect with the ClubGearHub community on our Discord server and join our mailing list for the latest updates and discussions. Engage with fellow enthusiasts, share your experiences, and be part of a vibrant community dedicated to improving equipment management for clubs.</p>
  </li>
</ol>

<p>We invite you to explore the ClubGearHub Open Source Website and become an active member of our growing community. Your feedback and contributions are essential as we continue to enhance and refine ClubGearHub.</p>

<p>Thank you for being part of this exciting journey!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello ClubGearHub community,]]></summary></entry></feed>